[Music]
welcome back to the next christmas video
this one is all about not the baby
making noise in the background
is advocare this is a very popular drink
in england even though it's dutch i
think but the original
dutch version if i've got that right is
quite different to this it's a thick
horrible sauce and liqueur that they put
over things but um we won't go into that
this is a drink that i mean look it goes
perfect in
in my mousse glass
ah thinks about memories this
this was the first alcoholic drink i
think i ever had uh i'm not going to say
what age
my parents look bad no i'm going to say
it was 18.
um it's very simply 50 ml worth of this
topped up
with lemonade but on warnick's website
they've got some variations that you can
make
with this avocado so we're just going to
try a couple of those and see what
happens plus there's a little bit of a
um a nice treat in here which we'll go
into in a second
[Music]
so what what is it uh you know in its
essence like i said
it's 50 mil i'm not measuring this at
all
worth of the actual avocado itself
topped up with lemonade
and that is pretty much
it i haven't got a spoon so i'm not
gonna steer it
but that is your box standard it's the
same as what's in there
there's your box standard snowball
you're supposed to
[Music]
put some lime in it we're just gonna
decorate that
like that there we go very standard
snowball but
what i did the other day
i'm actually thinking about it i do have
a spoon just here
so we're just gonna very quickly give
that a bit of a stir
like so there we go i have
officially stirred this drink
i have made a couple of days ago some
advocate ice cream and i've not even
tried it yet as you can probably see
whether it's in focus or i don't know
and this is an eggless base with a
load of this in it and it smells
incredible i've also put some
marshmallows now what did i put in there
meringue meringue can't even remember
i've got a lot of ice cream in the
freezer i've put some meringue
into this so what would happen if
you made an ice cream float
out of your
[Music]
snowball here we go here come the
bubbles
maybe not let's just give it another
quick a quick stir
here we go that would happen at some
point
but you've got your standard snowball
with
i mean i don't even know what this
tastes like on its own let's let's try
the old bar spoon and get in there
you really can taste that avocado come
through nice little crunch
from the actual meringue in there as
well but i'll do it if you're interested
i'll do
a video of how to make this ice cream
separately but
for now variation
number two
[Music]
so that is the end of the second
variation
[Music]
nice big goal for that all in the
christmas beard
and one last variation we're gonna do is
an affigato
with it so we're gonna get our martini
glass out there you go
charlie have for that and an affigato
is an italian treat with ice cream with
espresso poured at the top of it
so we're going to take another good
scoop
of our avocado ice cream
put that in our glass
some freshly prepared and exceedingly
hot
espresso coffee poured over the top
and just to top it off this is
a avocado white chocolate sauce that i
made about 20 minutes ago
so we're going to scoop a nice big
chunk of that and plonk that on top
like so and there you have
the final variation
on your snowball
so if you are one of those people that
enjoys snowballs
in your house and you happen to have an
ice cream maker
then why not give this a shot because
this tastes incredible
nice bit of coffee mixes with the ice
cream really well that white chocolate
sauce is to die for well there you go
that's another little christmas
video how to do three different
variations
of your advocare we've got two more that
we've got planned we're gonna try and
film them tomorrow
the baby is actually being surprisingly
quiet in the background which is
heavenly and rather unusual um the next
two
are gonna be hot chocolate based so
keep your eyes out for those hopefully
get them up for next week
anyway thanks very much for watching and
if i don't see you next time
merry christmas